

ALWIN JOHNSON

Photographer & Cinematographer

About Me

I chase the fleeting moments of light and laughter, weaving them into timeless stories that transcend the frame. With a blend of whimsy and documentary precision, I capture the raw beauty of the human experience, from the quietest intimacies to the most exuberant celebrations. My work has touched the hearts of over 50 satisfied clients. I'm a passionate photographer and cinematographer specializing in event, and corporate shoots like Gallagher, and corporate event shoot for Zoho, Google, Novo Nordisk, also AD Shoot for Fitness centre. Convention Centre....

I am driven by a relentless pursuit of visual excellence. Let's collaborate to bring your vision to life.



+91 9562120301



allualwi4@gmail.com

Expertise

- Photography
- Cinematography
- Colour correction and retouching
- Video Editing
- Graphic Designing

Known Software

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Lightroom
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Corel Draw

Experience

Freelance Photographer (2021-2023)

Content creator at RUN Fellowship Church, Bangalore (2021-2022)

Assitant Photograher at Maxxo Creative, kochi (2022) (Internship)

Photographer at Dotting Eye, Bangalore (2023 - Now)

Education

2019 - 2020

Higher Secondary School (St.Antony's H.S.S. Kollam)

2020 - 2023

BA Visual

Communicatiom (Kristu Jayanti School, Bangalore North University)

Language

- English
- Malayalam
- Hindi (basic)

Reference

Rojor Manathoor

Director, Dotting Eye.

Phone: +91 9035402999

Email: Rojor@dottingeye.com